<Introduction>
    <Intro language="Russian">
        <symbol>ЭТА ПЛАНЕТА МОЖЕТ СТАТЬ ТВОИМ НОВЫМ ДОМОМ!</symbol>
	    <symbol>ВЫБЕРИ ЭТУ ПЛАНЕТУ, ЧТОБЫ ЗАСЕЛИТЬ ЕЁ!</symbol>
	    <symbol>НЕМНОГО ПОСТАРАЙСЯ, И ЭТА ПЛАНЕТА СТАНЕТ РАЕМ!</symbol>
	    <symbol>ДОМ, МИЛЫЙ ДОМ. МОЖЕТ, ЭТО ОБ ЭТОЙ ПЛАНЕТЕ?</symbol>
        <symbol>КАК ТЕБЕ ПЛАНЕТА? ПОХОЖЕ, ОТЛИЧНЫЙ ВАРИАНТ!</symbol>
        <symbol>НРАВИТСЯ ПЛАНЕТЫ? ВЫБЕРИ ЕЁ, ЧТОБЫ ЗАСЕЛИТЬ.</symbol>
        <symbol>ЭТА КРАСИВАЯ ПЛАНЕТА МОЖЕТ ПРИЮТИТЬ ТВОЙ НАРОД.</symbol>
        <symbol>КАПЕЛЬКА ТЕРПЕНИЯ, И ПЛАНЕТУ МОЖНО ЗАСЕЛЯТЬ.</symbol>
        <symbol>ЦЕЛЬ - НАЙТИ НОВЫЙ ДОМ. ЗАДАЧА ЯСНА.</symbol>
        <symbol>В ТВОИХ РУКАХ ЖИЗНЬ ЦЕЛОГО НАРОДА. ДЕЙСТВУЙ.</symbol>
        <symbol>ТВОЙ НАРОД ВЕРИТ ТЕБЕ И В ТЕБЯ.</symbol>
        <symbol>ИССЛЕДОВАТЬ, ДОБЫТЬ РЕСУРС, ПОВТОРИТЬ.</symbol>
        <symbol>ДУМАЙ МЕДЛЕННО. ДЕЙСТВУЙ БЫСТРО.</symbol>
        <symbol>ТЕБЕ НУЖНО СПАСТИ КАК МОЖНО БОЛЬШЕ ЖИТЕЛЕЙ.</symbol>
        <symbol>ОБЕСПЕЧЬ ПЛАНЕТУ РЕСУРСАМИ И ЗАСЕЛЯЙ ЕЁ.</symbol>
        <symbol>ЗА ТОБОЙ ВЫБОР ДОМА ДЛЯ ДЕТЕЙ ТВОЕГО НАРОДА.</symbol>
        <symbol>РАНЬШЕ НАЧНЕШЬ ПЕРЕСЕЛЕНИЕ - БОЛЬШЕ УСПЕЕШЬ.</symbol>
        <symbol>ПЕРЕВЕЗЕННЫЕ ЖИТЕЛИ БУДУТ ТЕБЕ БЛАГОДАРНЫ.</symbol>
        <symbol>ПОРА СВАЛИВАТЬ СО СВОЕЙ ПРОГНИВШЕЙ ПЛАНЕТЫ.</symbol>
        <symbol>ВОТ БЫ ПОСКОРЕЕ СТУПИТЬ НА НОВУЮ ПЛАНЕТУ!</symbol>
        <symbol>НОВАЯ ПЛАНЕТА - ЖИЗНЬ С ЧИСТОГО ЛИСТА.</symbol>
        <symbol>НИКОГДА НЕ СДАВАЙСЯ, ГОВОРИЛИ ОНИ. КАК ЖЕ.</symbol>
        <symbol>МНЕ УЖЕ СНИТСЯ ЖИЗНЬ НА НОВОЙ ПЛАНЕТЕ. А ТЕБЕ?</symbol>
        <symbol>СПАСИ НАРОД, И О ТЕБЕ БУДУТ СКЛАДЫВАТЬ ЛЕГЕНДЫ!</symbol>
        <symbol>С ИССЛЕДОВАННОЙ ПЛАНЕТЫ МОЖНО ЗАБРАТЬ РЕСУРС.</symbol>
        <symbol>ЭФИРНЫЙ РЕСУРС МОЖНО ПРЕВРАТИТЬ ВО ЧТО УГОДНО.</symbol>
        <symbol>НЕ ИГНОРИРУЙ ПЛАНЕТЫ С НИЗКИМ ТЕРРАИНДЕКСОМ.</symbol>
    </Intro>
    <Intro language="English">
        <symbol>This planet may become your new home!</symbol>
        <symbol>Choose the planet to populate it!</symbol>
        <symbol>Exert oneself to make this planet a paradise!</symbol>
        <symbol>Home, sweet home. Is it about this planet?</symbol>
        <symbol>Do you like the planet? It Looks like a brilliant option!</symbol>
        <symbol>Do you LIKE THE PLANET? CHOOSE IT TO POPULATE</symbol>
        <symbol>THIS BEAUTIFUL PLANET CAN save YOUR PEOPLE</symbol>
        <symbol>A drop of patience, and the planet can be taken.</symbol>
        <symbol>The aim is TO FIND A NEW HOUSE. THE PROBLEM IS CLEAR.</symbol>
        <symbol>THE LIFE OF A WHOLE population IS IN YOUR HANDS. ACT.</symbol>
        <symbol>YOUR PEOPLE BELIEVE YOU.</symbol>
        <symbol>EXPLORE, GET RESOURCEs, REPEAT.</symbol>
        <symbol>THINK SLOWLY. ACT FAST.</symbol>
        <symbol>YOU NEED TO SAVE AS MANY OF RESIDENTS AS POSSIBLE.</symbol>
        <symbol>SUPPLY THE PLANET WITH RESOURCES AND POPULATE IT.</symbol>
        <symbol>CHOOSE A HOUSE FOR THE CHILDREN OF YOUR PEOPLE.</symbol>
        <symbol>TRANSPORTED RESIDENTS WILL BE GRATEFUL TO YOU.</symbol>
        <symbol>IT'S TIME TO LEAVE YOUR ROTTED PLANET</symbol>
        <symbol>YOU WOULD be HAPPY to STEP ON A NEW PLANET!</symbol>
        <symbol>NEW PLANET'll restart your LIFE.</symbol>
        <symbol>THEY SAID not to GIVE UP EVER. Of course</symbol>
        <symbol>I DREAM of the LIFE ON A NEW PLANET. What about YOU?</symbol>
        <symbol>SAVE THE PEOPLE, AND LEGENDS WILL BE FOLDING ABOUT YOU!</symbol>
        <symbol>You can TAKE A RESOURCE FROM THE EXPLORED PLANET</symbol>
        <symbol>ETHER CAN BE TURNED INTO ANY RESOURCE</symbol>
        <symbol>DON'T IGNORE LOW TERRAINDEX PLANETS</symbol>
    </Intro>
</Introduction>